Ashutosh Omble

ashuomble5@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/evilsempire in

https://github.com/evilsempire

Self-motivated web developer with a high level of experience working on multiple projects. Passionate and hardworking with a penchant for meeting deadlines. Interested in a role with a company that promotes best practices and offers a wealth of customer projects.

Skills/Technologies

- React IS
- PHP
- MySQL
- WordPress '
- Bootstrap
- AWS

- Node JS
- Postgres
- JavaScript/ HTML5/ CSS
- CodeIgniter
- SSL
- GIT Versioning

Experience

DEC 2019 - PRESENT

Node JS Developer / Travelex, Mumbai

- Design and configuration of the fully automated CI/CD lifecycle for the high-volume data transformation product for foreign exchange data.
- Maintaining newly developed and legacy systems high-volume external web app service applying knowledge of serverless framework using AWS lambda.
- Performing Unit & load testing for critical progressive web applications using various frameworks such as Cucumber, chai, mocha.
- Reviewing the quality of code for the high-volume applications build on NodeJS framework.
- Developed React Based frontend dashboard to monitor logs for file handling.

JUL 2017 - DEC 2019

Senior Web Developer / Pixels Agency, Mumbai

 Incorporate technical considerations into web sites design plans, such as budgets, equipment, performance requirements, or legal issues including accessibility and privacy.

- Used programming capabilities in ReactJS, Node JS, Postgres, PHP, SQL and JavaScript and other libraries as needed.
- Worked as a web developer for the company's dashboard to automate and manage orders, from inquiry phase till it's completed.
- Developed Dashboard and API in PHP, CodeIgniter using various frameworks for the Web application.
- Developed ERP systems with React js and node js framework.
- Created front end websites using the WordPress framework.
- Exposure for testing, deployment VPS, SSL, setup website.
- Install and configure the hypertext transfer protocol (HTTP) servers and associated operating systems.

2017 - PRESENT

Independent Web Developer / Self employed

Talent Arabia Jan 2021 – Present

https://talent-arabia.com

Talent Arabia is the fastest growing IT service providers, staffing solution and outsourcing company catering entire GCC - with our presence in UAE, Oman and India.

Sportzking Apr 2020 – Dec 2020

https://sportzking.com/

SportzKing runs free-to-enter daily contests based on real-life sports (cricket, football, baseball, MMA, basketball and many more) where you try to predict the results/outcomes of matches by entering the contests and answering the prediction-based questions. Questions can include predicting match winners, runs scored, goals scored, wickets taken, etc.

Lata Fibres Jan 2020 – Apr 2020

https://latafibres.com

As a leading organization in the textile industry of India, Lata Fibres Pvt Ltd, offer a wide and extensive range of products right from yarn, knitting, shirting's, uniforms & a lot more.

Aniket Baheti Apr 2020 - Present

https://aniketbaheti.com/

Aniket is an Entrepreneur & Blogger who has worked for multinationals and for startups, pursued different roles and functions, worked with diverse set of people.

Shree bungalows Jan 2018 - Jan 2018

http://www.shreebunglows.com/

Shree bungalows is beautiful website based on the hotel of the individual, where families can enjoy their vacation. This was the front-end website which shows the details about the hotel, also booking can be done via the website.

Education

JUN 2017

Computer science / Universal College Of engineering

GPA: 8.41

JUN 2013

Science (HSC) / Ismail Yusuf College, Mumbai

Percentage: 68.69

JUN 2011

Science (SSC) / Shree Samarth Vidyalaya, Mumbai

Percentage: 88.91

Activities

Web Developer Course with Seven Consultants and Technology Pvt.

Participated in 3rd National Level Paper Presentation Competition (IETE) on E-secured Documents and Sharing via QR code.